Contact

harthealr73@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tammy-rodriguez-a8026549 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
ACLS
BLS
Critical Care

Tammy Rodriguez

Vice President / CNO Metroplex Health System Copperas Cove, Texas

Summary

Experienced Vice President with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Physician Relations, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Critical Care Nursing, Healthcare Management, and Healthcare. Strong professional graduated from The University of Texas at Arlington.

Experience

AdventHealth
CNO / Vice President
January 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months)
Central Texas

Metroplex Health System makes successful transition to Advent Health Central Texas joining our Advent hospitals across the country #FeelingWhole

Metroplex Health System
CNO
January 2014 - Present (6 years 7 months)
Killeen, Texas

Metroplex Hospital
8 years 6 months

Director of Cardiovascular Services
June 2012 - January 2014 (1 year 8 months)

Director Cardiac Cath Lab August 2005 - June 2012 (6 years 11 months)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Masters Hospital Administration · (2013 - 2015)

The University of Texas at Arlington Working on BSN · (2010 - 2012)

Central Texas College
ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse